[{"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8ab", "answers": [{"answer": "light", "id": "BSuWm", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "soft", "id": "LwM45", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.055Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8ab", "question": "A ………… meal", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:35:59.928Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8ad", "answers": [{"answer": "heavy", "id": "Fqw0B", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "strong", "id": "wePB4", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.092Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8ad", "question": "A …….. meal", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:35:59.951Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8af", "answers": [{"answer": "fresh", "id": "OVNmd", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "new", "id": "BdZNA", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.106Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8af", "question": "………. bread", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:35:59.967Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8b1", "answers": [{"answer": "stale", "id": "i4EQ1", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "sour", "id": "NfMDK", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.117Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8b1", "question": "…….. bread", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:35:59.997Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8b3", "answers": [{"answer": "warm", "id": "Z26xl", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "hot", "id": "2DK1P", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.127Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8b3", "question": "……….. curry", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.006Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8b5", "answers": [{"answer": "mild", "id": "94DQF", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "soft", "id": "OaPxt", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.135Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8b5", "question": "…………. curry", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.016Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8b7", "answers": [{"answer": "pink", "id": "CoL14", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "sweet", "id": "o9jjM", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.143Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8b7", "question": "……… wine", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.024Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8b9", "answers": [{"answer": "main course", "id": "C6hen", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "main helping", "id": "gtROo", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "main meal", "id": "SH9hN", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.152Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8b9", "question": "The menu looks good. What are you going to order for your .………………..?", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.031Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8bb", "answers": [{"answer": "smashed potatoes", "id": "TN8uM", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "mashed potatoes", "id": "toray", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "minced potatoes", "id": "Bsvj4", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.162Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8bb", "question": "Would you like ………………. or chips with your steak?", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.039Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8bd", "answers": [{"answer": "freshly-cut", "id": "GmYpz", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "freshly-ground", "id": "UL1BA", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "freshly-powdered", "id": "SP2jh", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.170Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8bd", "question": "The smell of ……………… coffee woke up me this morning.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.051Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8bf", "answers": [{"answer": "lift up our glasses", "id": "t6SFv", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "empty a bottle", "id": "CRmBu", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "raise our glasses", "id": "nhFYF", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.179Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8bf", "question": "Let’s ……………….. and drink a toast to the happy couple !", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.082Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8c1", "answers": [{"answer": "having a strict diet", "id": "nXbWf", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "on a strict diet", "id": "UygDs", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "dieting strictly", "id": "lmQDX", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.188Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8c1", "question": "He’s …………….. because he wants to have a better attractive physical appearance.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.114Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8c3", "answers": [{"answer": "leaves", "id": "UGwRH", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "grounds", "id": "6bC9d", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "seeds", "id": "RGaTS", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "buds", "id": "xyNos", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.196Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8c3", "question": "My aunt could tell fortunes from tea ………….", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.140Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8c5", "answers": [{"answer": "smells", "id": "DX0Vi", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "senses", "id": "oyeYt", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "feels", "id": "BABvO", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "tastes", "id": "kJD4K", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.203Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8c5", "question": "This avocado ……… rather hard.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.162Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8c7", "answers": [{"answer": "appetizing", "id": "Gu3U4", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "nourishing", "id": "C2kFb", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "healthy", "id": "oi1uC", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "good", "id": "DyKiX", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.210Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8c7", "question": "Oranges are said to be ………….. for me but I don’t much like them.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.171Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8c9", "answers": [{"answer": "material", "id": "eYbCC", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "substance", "id": "i76Hg", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "solid", "id": "C21ik", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "powder", "id": "Ctv6Z", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.219Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8c9", "question": "In the jar there was a …………. Which looked like jam.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.182Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8cb", "answers": [{"answer": "drinks", "id": "7LW2M", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "foods", "id": "Ne2BF", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "meals", "id": "OOPGC", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "refreshments", "id": "VyX3n", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.228Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8cb", "question": "Light ……. were served during the meeting interval.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.197Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8cd", "answers": [{"answer": "new", "id": "HwRbW", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "fresh", "id": "GZLK7", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "ripe", "id": "mgR0x", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": {"blocks": [{"depth": 0, "entityRanges": [], "inlineStyleRanges": [], "key": "fp9qg", "text": "young", "type": "unstyled"}]}, "id": "DROgz", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.236Z", "has_suggest_answer": false, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8cd", "question": "These are ……. potatoes, not the end of last season’s.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.211Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8cf", "answers": [{"answer": "bowls", "id": "awNb6", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "dishes", "id": "ojiO6", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "plates", "id": "RTZhH", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "courses", "id": "pyWpK", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.244Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8cf", "question": "Pork chops are one of my favorite …………", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.221Z"}, {"__v": 0, "_id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8d1", "answers": [{"answer": "have", "id": "jMPF8", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "eat", "id": "PAxrR", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "consume", "id": "zGGxZ", "type": "editor"}, {"answer": "take", "id": "lsTkD", "type": "editor"}], "created_at": "2017-08-23T15:22:32.251Z", "has_suggest_answer": true, "id": "599d9db84a9c7f202d2dd8d1", "question": "I usually …….. white for breakfast.", "type": "multiple_choose", "updated_at": "2017-08-23T15:36:00.230Z"}]